Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive,
- Series IX. Music collection
  - 12 inch vinyl
    - Numbered by Bambaataa
      - 1277 - Soca explosion, 1978; SR-9390; Lord Shorty, 1941-2000. (Box 134)
      - 1279 - Genie, 1977; SR-9391; Lyle, Bobby. (Box 134)
      - 1280 - Presenting the Gary Byrd experience., 1972; SR-9392; Byrd, Gary (Vocalist) (Box 134)
      - 1281 - Different strokes, 1972; SR-9393; Nite-Liters (Musical group) (Box 134)
      - 1282 - Edwin Starr., 1977; SR-9394; Starr, Edwin. (Box 134)
        From The 20th Century Album Edwin Starr - T-538.
      - 1283 - Eddie Kendricks., 1973; SR-9395; Kendricks, Eddie. (Box 134)
      - 1284 - Unmistakably Lou, 1977; SR-9396; Rawls, Lou. (Box 134)
      - 1285 - You know you're wrong don't you brother, 1975; SR-9397; Heath, Walter. (Box 134)
      - 1286 - Castles in the sky, 1975; SR-9398; Futures (Musical group) (Box 134)
      - 1287 - Burning of Atlanta, 1973; SR-9399; Spirit of Atlanta (Musical group) (Box 134)
      - 1288 - Come into knowledge, 1977; SR-9401; RAMP (Musical group) (Box 135)
        Blue Thumb Records
      - 1289 - Fantastic Chi-Lites., 1977; SR-9402; Chi-Lites (Musical group) (Box 135)
      - 1290 - Three thousand miles from home, 1977; SR-9403; New York Port Authority (Musical group) (Box 135)
        Invictus
      - 1291 - We've got love, 1977; SR-9404; Smiley, Tommy. (Box 135)
      - 1292 - In my stride, 1977; SR-9405; Ruffin, David. (Box 135)
      - 1293 - Kung Fu fighting and other great love songs, 1974; SR-9406; Douglas, Californiarl. (Box 135)
      - 1294 - Moments with you, 1976; SR-9407; Moments (Musical group) (Box 135)
      - 1295 - Rest of my life, 1976; SR-9408; Reeves, Martha. (Box 135)
      - 1296 - Consider the Source, 1976; SR-9409; Creative Source (Musical group) (Box 135)
      - 1297 - Ebonys., 1976; SR-9410; Ebonys (Musical group) (Box 135)
      - 1298 - It's rough out here, 1975; SR-9411; Modulations (Musical group) (Box 135)
      - 1299 - This is your life, 1977; SR-9412; Connors, Norman. (Box 135)
      - 1300 - Moments live at Miss Black America Pageant., 1972; SR-9413; Moments (Musical group) (Box 135)
      - 1301 - Double my pleasure, 1978; SR-9141; Haywood, Leon. (Box 135)
      - 1302 - Pick of the litter, 1975; SR-9415; Spinners (Musical group: U.S.) (Box 135)
      - 1303 - Under my wings, 1972; SR-9416; Smith Connection (Musical group) (Box 135)
      - 1304 - Spark of love, 1978; SR-9417; Williams, Lenny. (Box 135)
      - 1305 - Love vibrations, 1978; SR-9418; Simon, Joe (Vocalist) (Box 135)
      - 1307 - My name is Caroline, 1978; SR-9419; Crawford, Californiaroline (Vocalist) (Box 135)
      - 1308 - Supernatural high, 1978; SR-9420; Payne, Freda. (Box 135)
      - 1309 - Ready to roll, 1978; SR-9421; Houston, Thelma. (Box 135)
      - 1310 - Man and boy., 1971; SR-9422-9423; Johnson, J. J., 1924-2001. (Box 135)
      - 1311 - Machine gun, 1974; SR-9424-9425; Commodores (Musical group) (Box 135)
      - 1312 - Party freaks, 1974; SR-9426; Miami (Musical group) (Box 135)
      - 1313 - New worlds, 1978; SR-9428; Mandrill (Musical group), (Box 135)
      - 1313 - Streamline, 1978; SR-9427; White, Lenny. (Box 135)
      - 1315 - My queen, 1978; SR-9429-9430; Gaston (Musical group) (Box 135)
        Hot Wax
      - 1316 - Crystal world, 1975; SR-9431; Crystal Grass (Musical group) (Box 135)
      - 1317 - Let the music play-- for ever and ever, 1978; SR-9432; Arpeggio (Musical group) (Box 135)
      - 1318 - Crazy legs, 1973; SR-9433-9434; Austin, Donald. (Box 135)
        Dynamic Sounds Recording Co.
      - 1319 - In harmony, 1974; SR-6950; Irvine, Weldon. (Box 135)
        Strata-East
      - 1320 - Mysticism and romance, 1978; SR-9435; Newton, Tony (Antonio) (Box 135)
        My World Records
      - 1321 - Get your wings, 1993; SR-9665-9666; Aerosmith (Musical group) (Box 141)
        Reissue of: Columbia JC 32847 (p1974)._x000D_
      - 1322 - Callin', 1978; SR-9436; Pips (Musical group) (Box 135)
      - 1324 - All the woo in the world, 1978; SR-9437-9438; Worrell, Bernie. (Box 135)
      - 1326 - Bustin' loose, 1979; SR-9439; Brown, Chuck, 1936-2012. (Box 135)
        Source Records
      - 1327 - Follow the rainbow, 1979; SR-9440-9441; Duke, George. (Box 135)
      - 1328 - 'Bout love, 1978; SR-9442; Withers, Bill. (Box 135)
      - 1330 - Breakwater, 1978; SR-9443-9444 (Box 135)
      - 1331 - On the corner, 1979; SR-9445; Mack, Jimmie. (Box 135)
      - 1332 - Dancing in the fire, 1978; SR-9446-9447; Delilah (Singer) (Box 135)
        ABC Records: Sunshine Records X
      - 1333 - Life for the taking., 1978; SR-9448 (Box 136)
      - 1335 - Funky snakefoot, 1974; SR-9451-9452; Mouzon, Alphonse. (Box 136)
      - 1334 - Movin', 1974; SR-9449-9450; Southside Movement (Musical group) (Box 136)
      - 1336 - Sha na na now!, 1975; SR-9453-9454; Sha Na Na (Musical group) (Box 136)
      - 1337 - I'm a man, 1978; SR-9455; Macho (Musical group) (Box 136)
      - 1338 - Delights of the garden, 1977; SR-9456; Last Poets (Group) (Box 136)
        Douglas
      - 1339 - House of love, 1978; SR-9457; Staton, Californiandi. (Box 136)
      - 1340 - Fantasy, 1978; SR-9458; Aquarian Dream (Musical group) (Box 136)
      - 1342 - Hot streets, 1978; SR-9459; Chicago (Musical group) (Box 136)
      - 1343 - Gichy Dan's Beachwood #9., 1979; SR-9460 (Box 136)
      - 1344 - Spirit in the sky, 1969; SR-9461; Greenbaum, Norman. (Box 136)
      - 1345 - Feel no fret, 1979; SR-9462 (Box 136)
      - 1346 - Blue Note live at the Roxy., 1976; SR-9463-9464-9465 (Box 136)
      - 1348 - Jazz, 1978; SR-9466-9467; Queen (Musical group), (Box 136)
      - 1349 - Feets don't fail me now, 1979; SR-9469; Hancock, Herbie, 1940- (Box 136)
      - 1349 - Feets don't fail me now, 1979; SR-9468; Hancock, Herbie, 1940- (Box 136)
      - 1350 - Since before our time, 1978; SR-9470; Osiris (Musical group) (Box 136)
      - 1351 - Uncle Louie's here, 1979; SR-9471; Murphy, Walter, 1952- (Box 136)
      - 1352 - Brite lites, big city., 1979; SR-9472-9473 (Box 136)
      - 1353 - Mother factor., 1978; SR-9474 (Box 136)
      - 1354 - Edwin Birdsong., 1978; SR-9475 (Box 136)
      - 1355; "This copy used on the Renegades of Rhythm Tour featuring highlights of Afrika Bamba - Let me show you, 1976; SR-6882; Williams, Esther (Singer) (Box 5)
      - 1358 - Million dollar disco, 1979; SR-9476; Rare Gems (Musical group) (Box 136)
        California Gold
      - 1359 - Top ranking, 1977; SR-9477; Dillinger. (Box 136)
        Third World
      - 1360 - Dance my way to your heart, 1979; SR-9478; Soussan, Simon, (Box 136)
        "D.J. copy. Not for sale."
        Primo Records
        Milano, Italy
      - 1361 - Music of the sun., 1978; SR-9479 (Box 136)
      - 1363 - Handy dandy man., 1978; SR-9480 (Box 136)
      - 1364 - Skyy., 1979; SR-9481; Skyy (Musical group) (Box 136)
        Promotion copy. Not for Sale.
        SalSoul Records
      - 1364 - Skyy., 1979; SR-9482 (Box 136)
      - 1365 - Reggie Knighton Band., 1978; SR-9551 (Box 138)
      - 1365 - Reggie Knighton Band., Reggie Knighton Band (Box 136)
      - 1366 - Love satellite., 1978; SR-9483; Foster, Ronnie. (Box 136)
      - 1367 - Hot, wet and sticky, 1978; SR-9484; Galaxy (Funk group) (Box 136)
        "DJ copy, Loaned for promotion only" Matrix / Runout (Side 1 - label): AB 4211 SA; Matrix / Runout (Side 2 - label): AB 4211 SB.
      - 1369 - Invasion of the booty snatchers, 1979; SR-9485-9486; Parlet (Musical group) (Box 136)
      - 1370 - Crowd Pleasers., 1979; SR-9487 (Box 136)
      - 1371 - M3000, 1979; SR-9488; Mandre¿¿. (Box 136)
      - 1372 - Happy feet., 1979; SR-9489 (Box 136)
      - 1373 - Barry White presents Mr. Danny Pearson., 1978; SR-9490 (Box 136)
        Unlimited Gold
      - 1375 - What cha gonna do with my lovin', 1979; SR-9491; Mills, Stephanie, 1957- (Box 136)
      - 1377 - Disco spectacular, 1979; SR-9492; MacDermot, Galt. (Box 136)
      - 1378 - Promise of love, 1978; SR-9493; Delegation (Musical group) (Box 136)
        Shady Brook
      - 1379 - Disco madness., 1979; SR-9494-9495; Salsoul Orchestra. (Box 136)
        Promotional DJ copy._x000D_
      - 1380 - Good stuff, 1975; SR-9496; Imaginations (Musical group) (Box 137)
      - 1382 - Midnight energy., 1979; SR-9497 (Box 137)
        SMI Records
      - 1383 - Wardell Piper, 1979; SR-9498-9499; Piper, Wardell, (Box 137)
      - 1384 - Magic man., 1979; SR-9500 (Box 137)
        Hilda
      - 1384 - Magic man., 1979; SR-9501 (Box 137)
        Hilltak Records
      - 1385 - Warriors., 1979; SR-9502; De Vorzon, Barry. (Box 137)
        A & M Records: SP-4761 (Matrix: SP-5259--SP-5260)._x000D_
      - 1386 - Dancing and singing for you, 1978; SR-9503; Starfire (Musical group) (Box 137)
        Dynamic
      - 1387 - Black sheep, 1979; SR-9504; Hammer, Jan. (Box 137)
      - 1388 - Only the wild survive, 1979; SR-9505 (Box 137)
      - 1390 - Final thing, 1978; SR-9506 (Box 137)
        "Promotional copy. Not for sale"
      - 1391 - III, 1979; SR-9507; Shotgun (Musical group) (Box 137)
      - 1393 - Moment's pleasure., 1979; SR-9508; Jackson, Millie. (Box 137)
      - 1395 - Alley & the soul sneekers., 1979; SR-9509 (Box 137)
      - 1396 - Burn me up, 1979; SR-9510 (Box 137)
      - 1398 - Southern Cookin', 1979; SR-9511 (Box 137)
      - 1399 - YBS., 1979; SR-9512; Yates Brothers & Sisters. (Box 137)
        Ariola Records
      - 1400 - Rockie Robbins, 1979; SR-9513-9514; Robbins, Rockie, (Box 137)
        "Promotion not for sale"--disc label._x000D_
      - 1401 - Lady night, 1979; SR-9516; Juvet, Patrick (Vocalist) (Box 137)
        Promotional copy. Not for Sale.
      - 1401 - Lady night, 1979; SR-9515; Juvet, Patrick (Vocalist) (Box 137)
      - 1403 - Love at first bite: music from the original motion picture soundtrack, 1979; SR-9517; Bernstein, Charles, (Box 137)
        PAP Records
      - 1404 - Douce is loose, 1979; SR-9518; Doucette (Musical group) (Box 137)
      - 1405 - All in fun, 1979; SR-9519; Writers (Musical group) (Box 137)
      - 1406 - What the-- you mean I can't sing?!, 1974; SR-9520-9521; Van Peebles, Melvin, 1932- (Box 137)
      - 1408 - Straight to the point, 1979; SR-9522 (Box 137)
        White label promo.
      - 1409 - Wornell Jones., 1979; SR-9523-9524; Jones, Wornell, (Box 137)
        Parachute Records
      - 1412 - Trenchtown mix up, 1976; SR-9525; Gladiators (Musical group), (Box 137)
      - 1413 - Philly Cream., 1979; SR-9527; Philly Cream (Musical group) (Box 137)
      - 1413 - Philly Cream., 1979; SR-9526; Philly Cream (Musical group) (Box 137)
        Fantasy WMOT Records
      - 1415 - Smokin', 1979; SR-9528; Undisputed Truth (Musical group), (Box 137)
      - 1416 - Funky entertainment, 1979; SR-9529-9530 (Box 137)
        CBS Inc.
      - 1421 - Paris Connection., 1978; SR-9531 (Box 137)
      - 1422 - Rainbow visions., 1978; SR-9532 (Box 137)
      - 1423 - Sweet, sweet city rhythm, 1978; SR-9533; Fantasia (Disco group) (Box 137)
      - 1424 - Yellow submarine, SR-9534 (Box 137)
      - 1425 - Bustin' outta the ghetto, 1970; SR-9535; Malcolm, Californiarlos, 1934 or 1935- (Box 137)
        AJP
      - 1426 - Bombers 2, 1979; SR-9536-9537; Bombers (Disco group) (Box 137)
        Promotion copy; not for sale.
      - 1428 - New sounds of the Louis Prima Band., 1968; SR-7037; Prima, Louis, 1910-1978. (Box 19)
        Delicious Vinyl
      - 1429 - Willie remembers., 1972; SR-9538-9539; Rare Earth (Musical group) (Box 137)
      - 1430 - Band kept playing, 1974; SR-9540; Electric Flag (Musical group) (Box 137)
      - 1431 - Camel in the city, 1979; SR-9541; Quartz (Musical group) (Box 137)
      - 1432 - Light of life, 1978; SR-9542; Bar-Kays (Musical group) (Box 137)
      - 1434 - Mutiny on the mamaship, 1979; SR-9543; Mutiny (Musical group) (Box 137)
      - 1435 - Locker room, 1979; SR-9544; Double Exposure (Musical group) (Box 137)
      - 1436 - New values, 1979; SR-9545-9546; Pop, Iggy, 1947- (Box 138)
      - 1438 - Spooks in space, 1979; SR-9547; Aural Exciters (Musical group) (Box 138)
        ZE Records
      - 1439 - Climbin' higher, 1979; SR-9548-9549; 7th Wonder (Musical group) (Box 138)
        Promotional DJ copy.
      - 1440 - Joy ride, 1979; SR-9551; Brooklyn Dreams (Musical group) (Box 138)
      - 1441 - Chapter 8., 1979; SR-9552; Chapter 8 (Musical group) (Box 138)
      - 1442 - TTF., 1979; SR-9553-9554 (Box 138)
      - 1443 - Going through the motions, 1979; SR-9555; Hot Chocolate (Musical group: 1970-) (Box 138)
      - 1444 - Original motion picture soundtrack "Buck Rogers", 1979; SR-9556; Phillips, Stu. (Box 138)
      - 1445 - Secret omen, 1979; SR-9557; Cameo (Musical group) (Box 138)
      - 1446 - Welcome to the world of Riot., 1974; SR-9558; Riot (Funk group) (Box 138)
      - 1447 - This boot is made for fonk-n, 1979; SR-9559; Bootsy's Rubber Band. (Box 138)
      - 1448 - My kids., 1979; SR-9560 (Box 138)
      - 1449 - Pado & Co., 1978; SR-9561; Pado & Co. (Box 138)
        Makossa International Records
      - 1450 - Get up, 1979; SR-9562; McGilpin, Bob. (Box 138)
      - 1451 - Chance to dance, 1979; SR-9563; Aquarian Dream (Musical group) (Box 138)
      - 1452 - Suite lady., 1978; SR-956f4 (Box 138)
      - 1454 - In danceland, 1979; SR-9567; Lucas, Californiarrie. (Box 138)
        Solar; Distributed by RCA Records
      - 1455 - Downwind, 1978; SR-9568-9569; Pierre Moerlen's Gong (Musical group) (Box 138)
      - 1455 - Downwind, Pierre Moerlen's Gong (Musical group) (Box 138)
      - 1458 - Wuthering heights, 1979; SR-9570; Ferrara, John. (Box 138)
      - 1460 - Anytime, anyplace, 1979; SR-9572; Dramatics (Musical group) (Box 138)
      - 1462 - You control me, 1979; SR-9573; Evans, Linda (Vocalist) (Box 138)
      - 1463 - Steppin' out, 1979; SR-9574; Osmonds (Musical group) (Box 138)
      - 1464 - Street angel, 1979; SR-9575; Rabb, Luther. (Box 138)
      - 1466 - Kebekelektrik, 1978; SR-9577 (Box 138)
      - 1467 - Switch II., 1979; SR-9578; Switch (Musical group) (Box 138)
      - 1468 - Come on inside, 1979; SR-9579; Scott, Rena. (Box 138)
      - 1469 - Dancin' with Melba, 1979; SR-9580; Moore, Melba. (Box 138)
      - 1470 - Evidence., 1979; SR-9581; Evidence (Disco group) (Box 138)
      - 1471 - It's time, 1979; Platinum Hook (Musical group) (Box 138)
      - 1472 - Jimmy Dockett's different moods., 1979; SR-9583; Dockett, Jimmy. (Box 138)
        Star Vision International
      - 1473 - Triple "S" Connection., 1979; SR-9584; Triple "S" Connection (Musical group) (Box 138)
      - 1474 - Never gonna be the same, 1979; SR-9585; Waters, Ruth (Singer) (Box 138)
      - 1475 - Montreal: featuring Uchenna Ikejiani., 1979; SR-9586; Montreal (Disco group) (Box 138)
      - 1477 - Love you forever, 1979; SR-9587; Castle, David (David D.) (Box 138)
      - 1478 - Me 'n rock 'n roll are here to stay, 1974; SR-9588; Ruffin, David. (Box 138)
      - 1479 - Stealin' home, 1975; SR-9589; Babe Ruth (Musical group) (Box 138)
      - 1481 - Salsa: original sound track recording., 1976; SR-9590-9591; Fania All Stars. (Box 138)
        Fania: SLP 00481 (on container: JM-00481).
      - 1482 - Bustin out., 1972; SR-9592 (Box 138)
        Tico Recording Company
      - Beat, the rhyme, the noise, 1989; SR-20841; Wee Papa Girl Rappers. (Box 138)
        Jive
      - 1484 - Booker T. set, 1969; SR-9594-9595; Booker T. & the MG's (Musical group) (Box 139)
      - 1486 - Life, 1970-1979; SR-9596; New Bermuda Stealers (Musical group) (Box 139)
        Editions Makossa International
      - 1487 - Carnival experience, 1979; SR-9597; Lee, Byron. (Box 139)
      - 1491 - Mass fever., 1979; SR-9598; Calypso Rose. (Box 139)
      - 1496 - On the radio--greatest hits: vol. I & II, 1979; SR-9599-9600; Summer, Donna, (Box 139)
      - 1498 - Devotion., 1979; SR-9601 (Box 139)
      - 1500 - Emotion, 1980; SR-9602 (Box 139)
      - 1501 - American gigolo: original soundtrack recording, 1980; SR-9603; Moroder, Giorgio. (Box 139)
      - 1501 - American gigolo: original soundtrack recording, 1980; SR-9604; Moroder, Giorgio. (Box 139)
      - 1502; This copy used on the Renegades of Rhythm Tour featuring highlights of Afrika Bambaataa's personal collection of soun - Pleasure principle, 1979; SR-6923-SR-6924; Numan, Gary, 1958- (Box 6)
      - 1503 - Jerry Knight., 1980; SR-9605 (Box 139)
      - 1504 - Ultimate., 1980; SR-9606 (Box 139)
        Promotional copy, not for sale.
      - 1506 - Let me be your angel., 1980; SR-9607; Walden, Narada Michael. (Box 139)
      - 1507 - Hold on (to your dreams)., 1980; SR-9608 (Box 139)
      - 1508 - Collins and Collins., 1980; SR-9609 (Box 139)
      - 1509 - In concert: the best of Jimmy Cliff., 1976; SR-9610; Cliff, Jimmy. (Box 139)
      - 1512 - Cat in the hat, 1980; SR-9611; Caldwell, Bobby. (Box 139)
        Clouds
      - 1513 - Teddy live! Coast to coast, 1979; SR-9612-9613; Pendergrass, Teddy, (Box 139)
      - 1514 - Come into my life, 1973; SR-9614; Jackson, Jermaine. (Box 139)
      - 1516 - Go all the way, 1980; SR-9615; Isley Brothers, (Box 139)
      - 1517 - Renaissance., 1980; SR-9616-9617; ADC Band. (Box 139)
      - 1518 - Beginning, 1980; SR-9618 (Box 139)
      - Make it last; Follow the path, 1980; SR-9619; Midnight Star (Musical Group) (Box 139)
        Not numbered, housed with SR-9618. Not for Sale._x000D_ From the "Beginning" album BXL1-3491.
      - 1519 - Jeff Kutash & the Dancin' Machine., 1980; SR-9620; Kutash, Jeff. (Box 139)
      - 1520 - Jermaine., 1972; SR-9621 (Box 139)
      - 1522 - Special edition., 1980; SR-9622 (Box 139)
      - 1525 - Big fun, 1979; SR-9623; Shalamar (Musical group) (Box 139)
      - 1526 - Eddie Money., 1977; SR-9624 (Box 139)
      - 1527 - S.O.S., 1980; SR-9625; S.O.S. Band. (Box 139)
      - 1530 - Love awaits, 1979; SR-9626; Washington, Deborah. (Box 139)
        "Demonstration. Not for Sale"
      - 1531 - Candi Staton., 1980; SR-9627; Staton, Californiandi. (Box 139)
      - 1532 - Brother Ray is at it again, 1980; SR-9628; Charles, Ray, 1930-2004. (Box 139)
      - 1533 - Watson Beasley., 1980; SR-9629 (Box 139)
      - 1535 - Let your mind be free, 1976; SR-9630; Brother to Brother (Soul group) (Box 139)
      - 1536 - Sweet sensation., 1980; SR-9631; Mills, Stephanie, 1957- (Box 139)
      - 1537 - Wide receiver, 1980; SR-9632; Henderson, Michael, 1951- (Box 139)
      - 1538 - Wanderer, 1980; SR-9633; Summer, Donna. (Box 139)
        Funky Tone
      - 1539 - Celebrate!, 1980; SR-9634-9635; Kool & the Gang, (Box 139)
        De-Lite
      - Take it to the top!, 1980; SR-9634-9635; Kool & the Gang, (Box 139)
        Not numbered, housed with SR-9634-9635. Promotion copy. Not for Sale._x000D_ From album DSR-9518 "Celebrate!"_x000D_ Both sides are identical.
      - 1540 - Skyy port., 1980; SR-9636-9637; Skyy (Musical group) (Box 139)
      - 1541 - 14 karat., 1980; SR-9638-9639; Fatback (Musical group) (Box 139)